export default {
  id: 'low_1006_3_2b',
  name: '상용한자(3학년-2/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:ゆび、さ(す)/음:し', answer: ['指'] },
    { question: '독:かわ/음:ひ', answer: ['皮'] },
    { question: '독:は/음:し', answer: ['歯'] },
    { question: '독:はな/음:び', answer: ['鼻'] },
    { question: '독:あ(る)/음:ゆう、う', answer: ['有'] },
    { question: '독:みじか(い)/음:たん', answer: ['短'] },
    { question: '독:あたた(か)、あたた(かい)、あたた(まる)、あたた(める)/음:おん', answer: ['温'] },
    { question: '독:くら(い)/음:あん', answer: ['暗'] },
    { question: '독:さ(る)/음:きょ、こ', answer: ['去'] },
    { question: '독:かえ(す)、かえ(る)/음:へん', answer: ['返'] },
    { question: '독:たす(ける)、たす(かる)、すけ/음:じょ', answer: ['助'] },
    { question: '독:ひろ(う)/음:しゅう、じゅう', answer: ['拾'] },
    { question: '독:も(つ)/음:じ', answer: ['持'] },
    { question: '독:お(きる)、お(こす)、お(こる)/음:き', answer: ['起'] },
    { question: '독:ひら(く)、ひら(ける)、あ(く)、あ(ける)/음:かい', answer: ['開'] },
    { question: '독:みずうみ/음:こ', answer: ['湖'] },
    { question: '독:きし/음:がん', answer: ['岸'] },
    { question: '독:ば(ける)、ば(かす)/음:か、け', answer: ['化'] },
    { question: '독:こおり、ひ/음:ひょう', answer: ['氷'] },
    { question: '독:あぶら/음:ゆ', answer: ['油'] },
    { question: '독:なみ/음:は', answer: ['波'] },
    { question: '독:곳집/음:こ、[く]', answer: ['庫'] },
    { question: '독:に/음:か', answer: ['荷'] },
    { question: '독:はこ/음:', answer: ['箱'] },
    { question: '독:ま(がる)、ま(げる)/음:きょく', answer: ['曲'] },
    { question: '독:つぎ、つ(ぐ)/음:じ、し', answer: ['次'] },
    { question: '독:はこ(ぶ)/음:うん', answer: ['運'] },
    { question: '독:부릴/음:やく、えき', answer: ['役'] },
    { question: '독:くる(しい)、くる(しむ)、くる(しめる)、にが(い)、にが(る)/음:く', answer: ['苦'] },
    { question: '독:うつく(しい)/음:び', answer: ['美'] },
    { question: '독:생각/음:そう、[そ]', answer: ['想'] },
    { question: '독:すみ/음:たん', answer: ['炭'] },
    { question: '독:はたけ、はた/음:', answer: ['畑'] },
    { question: '독:ね/음:こん', answer: ['根'] },
    { question: '독:ふか(い)、ふか(まる)、ふか(める)/음:しん', answer: ['深'] },
    { question: '독:う(える)、う(わる)/음:しょく', answer: ['植'] },
    { question: '독:볕/음:よう', answer: ['陽'] },
    { question: '독:は/음:よう', answer: ['葉'] },
    { question: '독:농사/음:のう', answer: ['農'] },
    { question: '독:みどり/음:りょく、[ろく]', answer: ['緑'] },
    { question: '독:あらかじ(め)/음:よ', answer: ['予'] },
    { question: '독:か(わる)、か(える)、しろ、よ/음:たい、だい', answer: ['代'] },
    { question: '독:もう(す)/음:しん', answer: ['申'] },
    { question: '독:가운데/음:おう', answer: ['央'] },
    { question: '독:そそ(ぐ)/음:ちゅう', answer: ['注'] },
    { question: '독:はしら/음:ちゅう', answer: ['柱'] },
    { question: '독:き(める)、き(まる)/음:けつ', answer: ['決'] },
    { question: '독:さか/음:はん', answer: ['坂'] },
    { question: '독:さら/음:', answer: ['皿'] },
    { question: '독:まめ/음:とう、[ず]', answer: ['豆'] },
    { question: '독:갖출/음:ぐ', answer: ['具'] },
    { question: '독:차례/음:だい', answer: ['第'] },
    { question: '독:큰 바다/음:よう', answer: ['洋'] },
    { question: '독:옷/음:ふく', answer: ['服'] },
    { question: '독:섬돌/음:かい', answer: ['階'] },
    { question: '독:わらべ/음:どう', answer: ['童'] },
    { question: '독:ゆ/음:とう', answer: ['湯'] },
    { question: '독:은/음:ぎん', answer: ['銀'] },
    { question: '독:ひつじ/음:よう', answer: ['羊'] },
    { question: '독:し(ぬ)/음:し', answer: ['死'] },
    { question: '독:よ/음:せい、せ', answer: ['世'] },
    { question: '독:지경/음:かい', answer: ['界'] },
    { question: '독:두/음:りょう', answer: ['両'] },
    { question: '독:よし/음:ゆ、ゆう、[ゆい]', answer: ['由'] },
    { question: '독:いた/음:はん、ばん', answer: ['板'] },
    { question: '독:등급/음:きゅう', answer: ['級'] },
    { question: '독:おもて、あらわ(す)、あらわ(れる)/음:ひょう', answer: ['表'] },
    { question: '독:おも、おもて、つら/음:めん', answer: ['面'] },
    { question: '독:고무래/음:ちょう、てい', answer: ['丁'] },
    { question: '독:구역/음:く', answer: ['区'] },
    { question: '독:고을/음:しゅう', answer: ['州'] },
    { question: '독:고을/음:けん', answer: ['県'] },
    { question: '독:みやこ/음:と、つ', answer: ['都'] },
    { question: '독:にわ/음:てい', answer: ['庭'] },
    { question: '독:ほか/음:た', answer: ['他'] },
    { question: '독:かな(しい)、かな(しむ)/음:ひ', answer: ['悲'] },
    { question: '독:힘쓸/음:べん', answer: ['勉'] },
    { question: '독:と(う)、と(い)、[とん]/음:もん', answer: ['問'] },
    { question: '독:글/음:しょう', answer: ['章'] },
    { question: '독:한수/음:かん', answer: ['漢'] },
    { question: '독:겨레/음:ぞく', answer: ['族'] },
    { question: '독:まも(る)、も(り)/음:しゅ、[す]', answer: ['守'] },
    { question: '독:むかし/음:せき、[しゃく]', answer: ['昔'] },
    { question: '독:まつ(る)、まつ(り)/음:さい', answer: ['祭'] },
    { question: '독:なご(む)、なご(やか)、やわ(らぐ)、やわ(らげる)/음:わ、[お]', answer: ['和'] },
    { question: '독:かか(る)、かか(り)/음:けい', answer: ['係'] },
    { question: '독:そだ(つ)、そだ(てる)、はぐく(む)/음:いく', answer: ['育'] },
    { question: '독:さだ(める)、さだ(まる)、さだ(か)/음:てい、じょう', answer: ['定'] },
    { question: '독:밝을/음:しょう', answer: ['昭'] },
    { question: '독:시간 단위/음:びょう', answer: ['秒'] },
    { question: '독:しら(べる)、ととの(う)、ととの(える)/음:ちょう', answer: ['調'] },
    { question: '독:ととの(う)、ととの(える)/음:せい', answer: ['整'] },
    { question: '독:さま/음:よう', answer: ['様'] },
    { question: '독:たび/음:ど、[と]、[たく]', answer: ['度'] },
    { question: '독:み、みの(る)/음:じつ', answer: ['実'] },
    { question: '독:ふえ/음:てき', answer: ['笛'] },
    { question: '독:みなと/음:こう', answer: ['港'] },
    { question: '독:よこ/음:おう', answer: ['横'] },
    { question: '독:곱/음:ばい', answer: ['倍'] },
    { question: '독:휘장/음:ちょう', answer: ['帳'] }
  ]
}
